fb101.com 2019-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Food & Beverage Magazine

**PRIVACY POLICY (06.29.2019)**

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.fb101.com

This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION, USE, and SHARING**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contacts from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to communicate with you, which includes the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

**YOUR ACCESS AND CONTROL OVER INFORMATION**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the contact form on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct/delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data. ** **

**SECURITY**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**REGISTRATION**

To use this website, a user may first be asked to complete a registration form. During registration, a user may be required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide other information (such as gender, age, etc.) about yourself, but it is not required.

**ORDERS**

We may request information from you on an order form, should one be added to this site. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you.

**COOKIES**

We may use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s previous visits to our website or other websites. 
    * Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).Google’s use of advertising cookies enables Google and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
    * Please note that third-party vendors and ad networks serve ads on this site, which currently include [Google](http://www.google.com/), [Rubicon Project](http://www.rubiconproject.com/) and [Taboola](http://www.taboola.com/) as of June, 2019
    * Users may visit these third-party websites to opt out of the use of cookies for personalized advertising (should the third-party or ad network offer this capability). Alternatively, you may also opt out of some third-party vendors’ uses of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) or [optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)

**SHARING**

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

**LINKS**  
This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**SURVEYS & CONTENTS**

From time-to-time, our site may request information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is voluntary, therefore, you may choose to participate and disclose information. The information requested may include contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level, etc.). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via our contact form on this web site.
